Kyle Rassweiler

Chone: +1-613-724-9141 | ■ Email: jobs@kylerassweiler.ca

(<u>b</u>) Code Camp: <u>https://www.freecodecamp.org/kylerassweiler</u>

Summary

Engineering Specialist with experience in: software development, networking, programmable logic controllers, robotics, electronics, and machining.

Skills

Software Angular, Apache2, Assembly(PIC), C++, CMake, Django, Git, HTML,

JavaScript, Meteor, Mongoose, Node, PHP, Python, React, Redux

Virtualisation Qemu/KVM, Docker, XCP-NG

Systems FreeBSD, Arch, Debian, Windows, Proxmox

Projects

KRello

A simple Trello clone developed using react and redux with jest and enzyme for testing. Used Javascript, SCSS, and HTML to style the react components.

Site: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/krello/

Demo: https://krello.kylerassweiler.com/
Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/krello

KR-Display

A responsive Meteor application for the display of SQL data. The system uses jobs to schedule information updates from the SQL server, the jobs then update the local MongoDB database. This dashboard displays production information, allowing managment to track and minimise downtime.

Site: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/kr-display/

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/kr-display

Kawasaki AS Parser

A Kawasaki robot backup parser written in TypeScript for browser or Node. The library also includes TypeScript interfaces for use in new projects.

Website: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/kawasaki-

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/kawasaki-as-parser

Robot Project Utility Mk2

A simple utility written in JS, HTML, CSS, React, and Electron(Node.js). The utility allows the user to view robot backup information from various robot brands(Currently Kawasaki), and is also used to compare two backups then determine any change points. The utility can also be used for work planning.

Site: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/software/robot-

project-utility/

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/robot-project-utility

Experience

Engineering Specialist

PLC programming, Robotic Vision (Robeye system), 3D Factory

Design, Robot programming, Project Management

2017 - Present

TEMA (Toyota)

Robotics Technician

PLC programming, Robot programming, SCADA programing.

2014 - 2017

FIO Automotive

Operational Technician PLC programming, Robot programming.

2012 - 2014

Abbott Point Of Care

Education

Responsive Web Design

Free Code Camp

2022 - 2022

Electro-Mechanical Engineering Technician Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON.

2010 - 2012

Computer Animation

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON.

2007 - 2010